[ silence ]
[ haunting voice ] ♪ Deedle , deedle , blackcoat 's daughter ♪
♪ What was in the holy water ? ♪
♪ Gone to bed on an unclean head ♪
♪ The angels , they forgot her ♪
[ eerie ambience ]
[ clacking footsteps ]
Daddy ...
You came early .
[ ominous music ]
[ Katherine ] Daddy , where 's the car ?
[ air hissing ]
Mommy ?
[ echoing ] Mommy ?
[ loud static ]
[ ominous ambience ]
[ quiet eerie music ]
[ phone ringing ]
[ secretary ] Father Brian ?
[ distant bell tolling ]
Sorry to disturb .
Yes ... of course .
Come in , Katherine .
Sit down .
Thank you , Dawn .
[ girls chattering outside ]
Mr. Walsh tells me that your recital
is coming along very , very nicely .
I 'm sorry that I won 't be around to see it .
But I 'm sure that
you 'll enjoy performing for your friends
and your parents all the same , won 't you ?
Where are you going ?
I have some personal business in Albany .
How long does it take to get to Albany ?
[ chuckles ]
Oh ... a couple of hours
by train .
So , about the same exact time
to come back , then , I guess .
Katherine ...
Are you concerned about something ?
No .
I mean I just wish you could stay
and see my performance .
That 's all .
Well , I 'm sorry , but this time ,
it just can 't be helped .
When do you come back ?
After the break
like everyone else , I should imagine .
Is something funny ?
Funny ?
No .
Why ?
You smiled a little .
I did ?
Yes .
You did .
Oh .
No .
I was just thinking to say
I hope you have a fun time in Albany .
[ eerie ambience ]
[ dark atmospheric music ]
[ shutter clicks ]
[ music fades ]
[ water running ]
[ water turns off ]
[ door squeaks open ]
[ door closes ]
Headache , you say ?
Yeah ...
And my throat kind of hurts when I swallow .
You poor thing .
It would be a shame to be sick over the break .
I know .
Here you are , dear .
[ Rose ] So , you really think I should tell him ?
Rose , of course you have to tell him .
It 's like half his . It 's half his problem anyway .
No it isn 't . Not really .
Well , it should be .
He 's the one that got you into this situation
in the first place .
He knew exactly what he was doing .
Like I didn 't ? He was doing it to me
and I was liking it .
[ laughs ]
Don 't laugh . It 's so not funny .
Besides , it 's only been four days .
I could still get it .
You think you 're gonna tell your parents ?
[ girls laughing in the distance ]
[ Mr. Gordon ] Of course
everyone is excited to have your parents come and
tour the classrooms and share your life
here at Bramford with them .
But that doesn 't mean there 's gonna be any change
when it comes to conduct expectations .
If anything , conduct is more important today
than any other day because
today we are all here representing Bramford .
That means you are representing
all of the young women who came before you
and all the young women who will follow you
after you 've moved on .
Sound good ?
[ all , lazily ] Sounds good .
[ Mr. Gordon ] And if I don 't see you before you leave ,
have a great week off
and we 'll see you back on the 22nd .
[ ominous ambience ]
[ people chattering ]
[ dark eerie music ]
[ indistinct chatter ]
Rose !
Where are you going ?
I was just gonna check out some of there performance .
- Are you okay ? - Yeah . Of course .
Where are your parents ?
They 're waiting inside , so I 'd better go .
Okay , well , I 'll see you next week then .
Okay ?
[ distant singing ] ♪ ... before I was born ... ♪
♪ ... the still waking morning , the tree was sown ♪
♪ But the lamb and the lion ♪
♪ were unnamed and unknown ... ♪
♪ She wore her ... ♪
♪ ... hair around her neck ♪
♪ at the foot of the bed where the lower things crept ♪
♪ ' neath a sea of white ... ♪
♪ ... roses her husband kept ♪
♪ Into the black night ♪
♪ In the garden beho ... ♪
[ phone ringing on other end ]
[ hangs up phone ]
Katherine , have you checked your cellular phone ?
Maybe they called there .
I don 't have one yet .
They said maybe for my birthday .
Oh .
Well ...
You know , bad weather coming in all over the East Coast , and
maybe they got caught up in that .
Planes get delayed ...
And Rose ? What about you ?
I thought we got out on Friday ,
so I told my parents to come on Friday .
Guess I spaced out .
Were you able to reach them ?
Yeah .
It just may take a day or so to change their plans .
A day ...
Yeah , ' cause
they were planning on coming on Friday , so they 'll
probably still come on Friday .
Oh , well ...
All right , well , Ms. Prescott and Ms. Drake
will be here in any case .
Now , do you hear that , Katherine ?
It happens that parents get confused , and
worst case is they come on Friday
and everyone goes home and has a really nice break anyway .
After all , we can 't let you live here .
Rose ...
Would you look after Kat until her parents arrive ?
I actually haven 't been feeling very well .
No ?
I have a really sore throat .
I was gonna stay in bed .
Oh .
Well ...
[ exhales audibly ]
Uh , Ms. Prescott ,
you will call Mr. Cornish in a few hours
both on his home phone and his mobile , won 't you ?
[ Ms. Prescott ] Of course we will .
Sound good ?
Katherine ...
Sounds good .
[ Katherine ] Hey ... Dad , uh ...
It 's me .
Just ...
Just calling to see where you and Mom are
and if you 're coming .
I guess you can call the school .
Okay .
[ clock ticking ]
Bye .
[ quiet music ]
[ ticking clock continues ]
[ ominous ambience builds ]
[ all together ] Dear Lord , thank you for this meal
that you have placed in front of us on this night ...
[ ominous ambience fades ]
[ music playing quietly ]
You know I 'm not babysitting you tonight , right , freshman ?
Mr. Gordon said you 're supposed to stay with me .
Yeah , but what 's he gonna to do ?
Bust me for not being at school over vacation ?
Mr. Gordon said ...
" Mr. Gordon said . Mr. Gordon said . "
What are you , a freaking recording ?
Where are you going ?
Me ?
Nowhere .
And if the Sisters say anything
just tell them I wasn 't feeling well
so I 'm staying in bed .
You do know about the Sisters , don 't you ?
Know what ?
You know they are wigs , right ?
You know that they have no hair on their bodies ?
No hair anywhere ?
Next time , check their eyebrows .
Totally fake .
The real ones
burnt right off .
That 's not true .
You didn 't hear about Jen Darling 's sister ?
Graduated three years ago .
She walked in on them one night
worshiping the devil .
Yeah .
Who told you ?
[ quiet ambient music ]
Don 't come in my room , okay ?
And don 't touch my shit .
[ engine idling ]
[ rock music playing inside car ]
[ ominous ambience ]
[ door creaks loudly ]
[ ominous ambience builds ]
[ phone rings ]
[ ominous ambience fades ]
[ bus engine idling ]
[ indistinct PA announcement ]
[ bus drives away ]
[ electricity buzzing quietly ]
[ eerie music ]
[ breathes audibly ]
[ disturbing ambience ] [ ghostly whispers ]
[ door handle jiggling ]
[ stammering ] There 's someone in here .
[ grunts ]
[ coins clattering ]
[ phone buttons beeping ]
[ phone ringing on other end ]
[ eerie music ]
[ recorded voice ] We 're sorry , but the number you have dialed
has been disconnected or is no longer in service .
If you feel that you may have reached this recording in error ...
[ eerie music continues ]
[ car engine idling ]
[ footsteps approaching ]
Hey ... are you okay ?
You can 't be warm enough in that jacket .
Are you waiting for someone ?
Can we give you a lift somewhere ?
You 've gotta be freezing .
Where 're you heading ?
We 're gonna go get back out on the highway ,
and then we 're gonna head east a little while .
How ' bout you . You heading someplace ?
Portsmith .
Sure .
I know Portsmith .
I 'm parked right over there .
My wife 's waiting in the car . See ? Right there .
My name 's Bill .
What 's your name ?
Joan .
My name 's Joan .
Jone ... Nice .
Nice name .
Bill ... what are you doing ?
Just trying to help .
Come on .
[ eerie ambience ]
We 'll take her to the next gas station .
[ Bill ] I 'm trying to help .
[ psychedelic rock music playing ]
[ exhales sharply ]
[ radio turns off ]
Call me later . Okay ?
I don 't have my phone .
So , that 's it ?
Stop saying that .
What am I supposed to say ?
Nothing .
I 'll take care of it .
Can you at least let me drive you there ?
No . No way .
Be careful .
Okay ?
Careful ...
Yeah , right .
[ door squeaks loudly ]
[ urine dribbling ]
[ whispers ] Idiot .
[ echoing thump , creaking sound ]
[ radiator softly hissing ]
[ muffled girl 's voice ] Sounds good .
[ muffled voice speaks indistinctly ]
[ radiator continues softly hissing ]
[ distant echoing thump ]
[ distant thumping noises ]
[ door creaks deeply ]
[ muffled voice speaks indistinctly again ]
[ door squeaks deeply ]
[ low distant creaking sound ]
[ muffled girl 's voice speaks indistinctly ]
[ deep creaking sound ]
[ door groans , slams ]
[ distant echoing thump ]
[ soft creaking sound ]
[ door squeaks loudly ]
[ muffled girl 's voice echoes indistinctly ]
Katherine ?
[ door creaks very loudly ]
[ door squeaks , shuts ]
[ muffled thumps ]
[ electricity buzzes ] [ distant thumping ]
[ muffled thumping , creaking continues ]
[ muffled girl 's voice speaks indistinctly ]
[ deep ominous ambience ]
[ ominous ambience building ]
[ eerie echoing crying , growling sounds ]
[ rumbling growl , loud groaning squeak ]
[ dissonant music building ]
[ screeching squeaks ]
[ screeching static squeak ]
[ eerie knocking ]
[ low rumbling slowly fades ]
[ distant muffled voices ]
[ sighs ]
[ muffled voices continue ]
[ exhales audibly ]
[ atonal music ]
[ loud gunshot ]
[ knock on door ]
[ exhales deeply ]
[ low ominous music ]
[ stammering ] Hello ?
[ muffled ] It 's Bill
from the bus station .
Do you mind if I come in ?
[ door closes ]
I just wanted to see how you 're doing .
[ sighs ]
I see you 're up , at least .
[ quiet ambient music ]
So ...
I guess you were pretty zonked out there , huh ?
You slept for almost four hours in the back seat .
I 'm sorry .
For what ?
First rule ...
You don 't apologize to me , young lady .
I 'm happy to help . Okay ?
I 'm sorry .
Okay .
Why are you doing this ?
Doing what ?
Helping me so much .
Do you believe in God , Joan ?
No .
No ? Just like that ?
Ever tried to look for Him ?
It 's strange ...
People think you look for Him in some book
or in a church or a statue .
Maybe even a candle flame ...
[ ominous ambience ]
But that 's not how it works for me .
I look for Him in the unlikely things that happen .
Little coincidences .
And when I saw you sitting at that bus station
you reminded me so much of someone .
Someone I haven 't seen in a long time .
And then ... when you said you were going to Portsmith
well ...
A coincidence like that , I just can 't ignore it .
So , strange as it may sound ...
I guess I saw God in you .
Are you going to Portsmith , too ?
No , not exactly .
Linda and I are headed to the town just before it .
We 're going to Bramford .
Do you know Bramford ?
[ eerie ambience continues ]
When do we leave ?
What 's that ?
What 's your hurry ?
Where 's your wife ?
She 's sleeping .
Why ?
[ eerie ambience fades ]
Well ...
Hopefully we can
get out of here first thing in the morning .
I , uh ...
Bet you 're pretty hungry .
Well , there 's a restaurant next door .
Why don 't you get dressed and come down and have some dinner ?
[ whispering ] Thank you .
Okay .
[ door opens , closes ]
[ eerie atonal music ]
[ shower running ]
Do you know how much trouble I could get into for this ?
[ shower turns off ]
[ water draining ]
Do you need a towel ?
So , what were you doing down there ?
Were you sleepwalking ?
Do you sleepwalk ? Is that what that was ?
Hello ?
[ Katherine ] Uh-huh .
What about your parents ?
Did they call ?
They 're not going to call .
They just got confused .
Like your parents ?
Mm-hmm .
But your parents didn 't get confused .
You told them not to come so you could go on a date .
It wasn 't a date .
It wasn 't ?
- No , it wasn 't . - What was it ?
It was nothing .
Mr. Gordon said you were supposed to look after me .
[ ominous ambience ]
I know what Mr. Gordon said .
Mr. Gordon said worst case they 'd be here by friday .
- Yeah , I know what he said . - But now it 's too late .
Too late for what ?
They 're dead .
What ?
That is an awful thing to say .
You shouldn 't say things like that .
Okay ? It 's just not funny .
You smell pretty .
You should go to bed .
Just go to bed , and then when you wake up in the morning ,
you 're gonna be okay .
All right ?
They 'll be here on Friday . They 're already on their way .
That 's it . Okay ?
That 's it .
You should go to bed now .
Is there anything else I can get you ?
No .
You had your chance .
[ ominous ambience builds ]
[ door squeaks ]
[ ominous ambience continues ]
[ eerie creaking ]
[ ghostly sounds ]
[ eerie ambience fades out ]
[ silverware , plates rattling ]
[ Bill ] There she is .
Linda has a extra coat .
It 's a lot warmer than yours
and she won 't mind if you borrow it .
She 's gonna be along any minute .
Thank you .
So , Portsmith , huh ?
Is that your home ?
Your mom and dad ?
[ quietly ] No .
No ?
Friends ? Someone ?
Someone .
Well , that 's better than having no one , isn 't it ?
[ chuckles ]
They changed the decor of this place a few years ago .
Used to be more of a ... kids place .
Famous for their chicken noodle soup .
That 's how we came by it , anyway .
Linda and I used to spend a lot of time here with our daughter .
Remember I told you that you , uh , reminded me of somebody ?
Well ...
You reminded me of her .
My daughter .
She 'd be right about your age by now .
We lost her nine years ago .
Nine years , uh ... tomorrow , actually .
And it 's okay . We-we do okay .
It 's difficult , but , uh ...
You know what they say . " Time heals all wounds " .
And little by little , it does get easier .
Except around this time of year when we go and lay flowers
on the anniversary .
I 've got a picture .
[ eerie music ]
Here .
[ Bill ] That 's my Rose .
She 's pretty .
Yes , she is . Isn 't she ?
[ waitress ] Have you decided ?
Oh , uh ... Yes , I 've decided .
Joan , have you decided ?
[ quietly ] Excuse me .
[ exhales audibly ]
[ giggles ]
[ ominous dissonant music ]
[ choking ]
[ eerie ambience ]
[ inaudible ]
[ Bill ] Oh , there you are .
Look , we 've got some , uh ,
really bad weather coming in over night ,
and if we don 't get on the road tonight
we 're gonna be snowed in tomorrow ,
maybe the day after .
They 're gonna pack up our food for us .
So why don 't you grab it and meet me out front ?
Okay ?
[ quietly ] Thank you .
[ soft clatter of silverware and plates ]
[ car idling ]
What did he tell you ?
Did he tell you about our daughter ?
When he told you about our daughter , he said ...
" have " ... didn 't he ?
We have a daughter .
[ softly ] Ve ...
[ sighing ] Ve ...
He told you you remind him of her .
He actually said that to you , didn 't he ?
[ quietly ] It 's okay .
Poor thing .
Tries to say that to everyone .
Of course I never see it .
Of course it isn 't true .
But ...
Still sometimes I try .
I saw it once .
I was at the supermarket alone
and I was standing
in the middle of a long aisle , all by myself ,
when a girl came around the corner .
She was looking at a low shelf for something .
She was about 15 .
She had
her money held tightly in her hand
like children do .
[ eerie ambience ]
I guess school had gone back already .
The weather had turned cold .
She was just in her
uniform skirt and sneakers with no socks .
Her knees were pink
almost red from the cold .
But what did she know ?
She had her hair in a ponytail
and I could see the roots
being pulled back from her ears .
[ inhales and exhales sharply ]
You don 't look anything like her .
It 's strange .
I can 't see you at all .
[ ominous ambience builds then fades ]
Okay .
[ wind blowing , birds chirping ]
[ door squeaks ]
[ phone receiver clatters down ]
Well , what did they say ?
What did they say ?
He said it 's all right .
What 's all right ? Who says ?
He says I can 't live here .
But I can ... with him .
Who 's " he " ?
[ quiet eerie ambience ]
You know who .
No , I don 't know .
Mr. Gordon ...
[ scoffs ] ... silly .
He 's the headmaster .
Oh .
You smell pretty .
[ silverware clatters ]
[ very quiet ambient music ]
[ clock ticking ]
Dear Lord , thank you for this meal
that you have placed in front of us on this day .
Katherine .
Yes , ma 'am ?
Is there something wrong ?
No , ma 'am .
In that case ,
kindly repeat grace for the rest of us .
[ clock ticking ]
[ whispering ] Dear Lord , um ...
Thank you for this meal that you have placed
in front of us that ...
[ scoffs ] ... and for which we are truly ...
Katherine !
[ ominous ambience building ]
[ deep eerie static ]
[ women gasping ]
Oh , mercy !
Is she okay ?
[ ominous ambience fades ]
She 's fine .
Did Mr. Gordon call ?
Why on Earth would the headmaster call here ?
I dunno , to ...
To say that they were all right ?
Her parents .
Of course they are all right .
And Katherine is all right as well .
Thank you , Ms. Drake .
Here , drink this , dear .
Katherine ?
Get your hands off me , cunt .
[ ominous ambience fades back in ]
[ phone rings ]
Ms. Drake ... the telephone , please .
Certainly , dear .
[ phone rings ]
[ Ms. Prescott ] You ought to be ashamed of yourself .
You will look at me when I am talking to you .
[ Ms. Drake ] Ms. Prescott , a word , please .
He really did say he 'd come .
He 'll come and he 'll say he as wrong .
[ speaking indistinctly ]
[ Katherine ] This time he 'll say that I can live here .
He 's the headmaster .
[ Ms. Prescott ] Rose , come out here , please .
I will kindly ask you to shovel the path between the houses .
Shovel it down to the earth .
[ Rose ] Me ?
Why me ?
What did I do ? She 's the one who called you ...
Mr. Gordon will be arriving later this afternoon .
Mr. Gordon ?
What happened ?
Down to the earth ... please .
[ ominous ambience ]
[ bird calls ]
[ shovel scraping , snow thumping ]
[ record player needle crackling ]
[ quiet ambient music playing inside ]
[ door rattling ]
[ silence ]
[ distant bell tolling ]
[ vehicle approaching ]
[ indistinct police radio chatter ]
[ brakes squeak ]
[ engine shuts off ]
Are you all right ?
Uh , yes .
They should be over this way .
[ door handle jiggles ]
[ knocking ]
[ record player needle scratching , crackling ]
Huh .
[ low , eerie music ]
[ record player continues crackling ]
[ doorknob turns , door squeaks ]
[ Mr. Gordon ] Ms. Prescott !
[ eerie music builds ]
[ music builds to screeching climax ]
[ music fades ]
[ playful shouting in the distance ]
[ distant applause ]
[ playful shouting continues ]
[ cheerleaders chanting in the distance ]
[ ambient music fades out ]
[ marker cap pops ]
[ marker squeaks ]
[ water dripping ]
[ ominous ambience fades in ]
[ ghostly whisper ]
[ ghostly whispers ]
[ coins clattering ]
[ buttons beeping ]
[ phone ringing on other end ]
[ click on phone ]
[ quiet static ]
Hello ?
Mommy ?
[ quiet static ]
Dad ?
[ deep , distorted voice on phone ] Hi , baby girl .
[ quiet static ]
Dad ?
[ deep , distorted voice ] Katherine .
[ soft static ]
Who-who is it ?
[ quiet static ]
[ static ]
Hello ?
[ deep , distorted voice ] They 're not coming .
[ soft static ]
[ deep , distorted voice ] Kill ... the cunts .
[ eerie ambience ]
[ foreboding atonal music ]
[ sound of a crowd muffled by atonal music ]
[ Rose 's voice , echoing ] ... they are wigs , right ?
You know that they have no hair on their bodies ?
No hair anywhere ?
Next time , check their eyebrows .
[ voice becoming more distorted ] Totally fake .
The real ones
burnt right off .
You didn 't hear about Jen Darling 's sister ?
Graduated three years ago .
She walked in on them one night
worshiping the devil .
[ intense distorted music ]
[ car idling ]
[ eerie music ]
[ phone rings ]
[ soft static on phone ]
Hi .
[ ominous ambience ]
[ deep , distorted voice on phone ] You can stay here with me .
[ distorted voice speaks indistinctly ]
[ gasping weakly ]
[ ominous droning ambience continues ]
[ deep , distorted voice speaks indistinctly ]
[ gasping weakly ]
[ weak gasping continues ]
[ squishing stab ] [ gasping ]
[ stab ] [ gasping ]
[ squishing stabs continue ]
[ weak gasp ]
[ ominous ambience fades out ]
[ eerie atmospheric music ]
[ shutter clicks ]
[ music fades out ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ softly ] Oh , my God .
Oh , my God .
[ laughs ]
[ door opens ]
Katherine ?
[ door squeaks , closes ]
[ door creaks ]
[ distant clicks ]
[ door squeaks ]
[ distressed breathing ]
[ dark dramatic music ]
[ squishing stabs ] [ Rose gasping ]
[ gasping scream ]
[ blood splattering ]
[ repeated stabbing ] [ gasping ]
[ blood squishing ]
[ soft gasping sobs ]
[ music fades out ]
[ birds calling ]
[ keys jingling ]
[ lock turns ] [ door squeaks ]
[ quiet atmospheric music ]
[ record player crackling softly ]
[ clock ticking ]
[ eerie atonal music ]
[ quiet breathing ] [ jingling ]
[ grunts softly ]
[ whispering ] Oh , Jesus Christ .
[ shuddering breaths ]
[ voice distorted ] Hey !
Hey , drop it !
[ panicked breaths ]
Hey , h-hey !
Hey , dro ... Hey , drop it .
[ panicked breaths ] D-drop it .
Drop the knife !
[ stammering ]
Drop the knife , God damn it !
This is your last warning ! I will shoot you !
[ eerie ambience ]
Drop the knife !
[ eerie music building ]
[ ghostly voice ] Hail Satan .
Hail Satan .
I said drop the knife !
[ demonic scream ] [ gunshot ]
[ eerie atmospheric music ]
Did you tell her ?
Did you tell her all about it ?
Please , Linda .
When you meet these people , do you say it ?
Do you say that she was murdered ?
Please !
[ Linda ] No , you don 't .
You don 't say
that when she was found they had to do a blood test
to see if her head matched the body .
- That 's enough ! - Just focus on the road .
Don 't touch me !
Can you please pull over ?
Huh ? What was that ?
I think I 'm gonna be sick .
Are you all right back there ?
Please pull over .
All right . Hold on .
Hold on .
No , please . Just go past it .
- We 're not stopping here . - Hold on , hold on .
God damn it , Bill ! Don 't stop here !
[ Bill ] Okay . [ Linda sobs ]
[ Bill ] Here we go .
[ crying ]
[ tense droning music ]
[ brakes squeak ]
[ inhales sharply ]
[ dramatic musical sting ] [ knife slitting ]
[ Linda crying out ] [ squishing stabs ]
[ stabbing ] [ crying out ]
[ ominous droning ambience ]
[ exhaling short breaths ]
[ retching , coughing ]
[ engine idling ]
[ shallow gasping breaths ]
[ dark tense music ]
[ car door opens ]
[ music fades ]
[ quiet ominous whine ]
Katherine ?
[ quiet suspenseful music ]
Shh .
[ dark atmospheric noise swells for a moment ]
There you are .
You are not wanted here .
I say
you will go from this place .
You will leave here .
[ Father Brian continues ] You will leave this poor girl
and you will never come back .
[ chains jingling ]
[ eerie ambience ]
[ haunting distorted music ]
[ Father Brian ] I command that you leave this place .
[ ghostly whispers ]
I command that you go out .
I command that you go out !
By the power of Christ I command you !
I command you to leave this girl
and never come back !
I command you to go out !
[ soft static crackling ]
[ soft static ] [ Katherine wheezes weakly ]
[ weakly ] Don 't go .
[ lighter flicks ]
[ eerie suspenseful hum ]
[ luggage thumps ]
[ lighter flicks ]
[ wind softly blowing ]
[ inhales sharply ]
[ crying quietly ]
[ anguished cry ]
[ anguished cry drown out by loud humming noise ]
[ crying inaudible over droning hum ]
[ silence ]
[ acoustic guitar music ]
♪ Deedle , deedle , blackcoat 's daughter ♪
♪ What was in the holy water ? ♪
♪ Gone to bed on an unclean head ♪
♪ The angels , they forgot her ♪
♪ Deedle , deedle , blackcoat 's daughter ♪
♪ What was in the holy water ? ♪
♪ Gone to bed on an unclean head ♪
♪ The angels , they forgot her ♪
[ song ends ]
[ dark ominous music ]